School of Engineering and Applied Science Records, 1884-2017: Finding Aid
Princeton University Library. Department of Rare Books and Special Collections.
- Series 1: Dean of the School of Engineering and Applied Science, 1896-2016 September 13; 149.37 linear feet 121 boxes Digital Folders: 97, Digital Files: 2,135 73,438 email messages
  - Subseries 1A: Kenneth H. Condit, 1920-1959; 23.75 linear feet 19 boxes
    - 'J' Miscellaneous, 1942-1953; 4 folders
      - 1951-1953, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 47)
      - 1947-1951, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 48)
    - Jahn, Nicholas F, 1943-1953; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 49)
    - Jeffries, Zay, 1940-1941; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 50)
    - Jewett, Frank B, 1943-1947; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 51)
    - Jiranek, Leo, 1951-1953; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 52)
    - Job Evaluation Committee, 1947; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 53)
    - Johnson and Johnson, 1946-1948; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 54)
    - Joint Research and Development Board, 1947; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 55)
    - Juran, J. M, 1944-1945; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 56)
    - Jones and Lamson Machine Company, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 57)
    - Jones, Thomas R, 1941-1952; 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 58)
    - 'K' Miscellaneous, 1943-1953; 4 folders
      - 1951-1953, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 59)
      - 1948-1950, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 60)
      - 1946-1948, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 61)
      - 1943-1947, 1 folder (Box 9, Folder 62)
    - Kassler, Kenneth, 1948; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Kellett Aircraft Corporation, 1941-1945; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Kenworthy, Nelson A, 1942; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Kenyon, John N, 1946-1950; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Kjetsaa, Chester, 1946-1958; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Knapp, William L, 1949; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Knoll, Max, 1948-1950; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Kwauk, Moosoon, 1944-1947; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - 'L' Miscellaneous, 1934-1955; 9 folders
      - 1944-1947, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 9)
      - 1943-1947, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 10)
      - 1944-1946, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 11)
      - 1934-1945, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 12)
      - 1948-1950, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 13)
      - 1950, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 14)
      - 1951-1952, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 15)
      - 1952-1953, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 16)
      - 1953-1955, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - Lambert, G. B, 1944; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - Lare, Charles S, 1946; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - Larkins, John Adrian, 1947-1949; 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 20 to 21)
    - Lawson, Edward Jr, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - Lebourveau, Willis A, 1948-1950; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - Lee Maurice DuPont, 1953; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - Leeds and Northrup Company, 1946-1950; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 25)
    - Lees, Lester, 1946-1953; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - Lehigh University, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - Leimdorfer, Doctor P, 1949; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - Lester, Bernard J, 1941-1946; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - Letters in Reference to Students, 1942-1945; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - Lincoln, James F., Arc Welding Foundation, 1947-1950; 1943-1947; 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 31 to 32)
    - Lindelow, William A, 1951-1953; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - Little-Murray-Barnhill Incorporated, 1941-1953; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - Loeb, Carl M. Jr, 1942-1949; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - Lukens Steel Company, 1944-1950; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - Lynch, John B, 1947-1953; 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - 'M' Miscellaneous, 1940-1955; more than 5 folders
      - 1940-1946, 2 folders (Box 10, Folder 38 to 39)
      - 1948-1950, 6 folders (Box 10, Folder 40 to 45)
      - 1951-1952, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 41)
      - 1952-1953, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 42)
      - 1953-1955, 1 folder (Box 10, Folder 43)
    - MacLaren, Malcolm, 1924-1945; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - MacMillan, Edward A, 1941-1947; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - MacMillan, Howard F, 1942-1945; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Madden, James E, 1944-1955; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Madden, James L, 1946-1950; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Madden, Richard B, 1950-1954; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Management Council, 1949; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Marine Corps Platoon Leaders Class Program, 1953; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Marine Corps Reserve, United States, 1942-1943; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Marshall, A. E, 1937-1944; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Martin, Harold C, 1942-1944; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Massachusetts Institute of Technology, 1942-1947; 2 folders
      - 1942-1947, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 12)
      - Visiting Committee, 1947; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Math Department, 1939-1948; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Mathematics, Engineering School Liaison Committee with the Department of, 1946; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 15)
    - Matthews Construction Company, 1951-1953; 1943-1944; 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 16 to 17)
    - Maute, Bernhard W, 1941-1945; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 18)
    - McAlpin, David H, 1942-1943; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 19)
    - McCully, Harry W, 1940-1950; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 20)
    - McGraw-Hill Publishing Company Incorporated, 1948-1950; 1941-1948; 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 21 to 22)
    - McIntosh and Seymour Company, 1931-1935; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 23)
    - McLean, Wallace D, 1951-1953; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 24)
    - McLure, N. R, 1937-1938; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 25)
    - McMillan Fund, Charles, 1924; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 26)
    - McMurray, John Coddington, 1949-1953; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 27)
    - Metallurgy, 1948-1952; 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 28 to 29)
    - Merritt-Chapman and Scott Corporation, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 30)
    - Merck, George W, 1940-1950; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 31)
    - Methods Engineering Council, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 32)
    - Meyer, Robert R, 1945; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 33)
    - Meyers, George R, 1941-1947; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 34)
    - Microcard Corporation, 1952; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 35)
    - Middle States Association, Colleges and Secondary Schools, 1951-1952; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 36)
    - Minneapolis Honeywell Regulator Company, 1951; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 37)
    - Monsanto Chemical Company, 1939-1946; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 38)
    - Monthly Payroll Assignment Sheets, 1946-1949; 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 39 to 40)
    - Moody, Lewis Ferry, 1941-1951; 1953; 2 folders (Box 11, Folder 41 to 42)
    - Mooney, James D. Sr. and Jr, 1942-1949; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 43)
    - Morgan Minot, 1942-1953; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 44)
    - Morgan, Sherley W, 1942-1945; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 45)
    - Morton Charles Hay, 1951; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 46)
    - Muench, John D, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 47)
    - Muir, Roy C, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 48)
    - Munn, John R, 1935-1950; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 49)
    - 'N' Miscellaneous, 1943-1954; 5 folders
      - 1951-1954, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 50)
      - 1948-1951, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 51)
      - 1946-1948, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 52)
      - 1945-1946, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 53)
      - 1943-1945, 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 54)
    - National Advisory Committee for Aeronautics, 1943-1947; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 55)
    - National Council of State Boards of Engineering Examiners, 1952; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 56)
    - National Defense Training, 1940-1942; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 57)
    - National Emergency Information, 1950; 2 folders
      - Faculty, 1950; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 58)
      - Non Faculty, 1950; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 59)
    - National Production Authority Priorities and Allocations, 1951; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 60)
    - National Research Council, 1942-1945; 1 folder (Box 11, Folder 61)
    - National Safety Council, 1940; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - National Science Foundation, 1947-1953; 2 folders
      - 1947, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 2)
      - 1952-1953, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Navy, 1940-1954; 7 folders
      - Bulkhead Project, 1943-1946; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 4)
      - David Taylor Model Basin, 1942-1947; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 5)
      - General Correspondence, 1940-1950; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 6)
      - General Correspondence, 1950-1954; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 7)
      - Pre-Radar Program, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 8)
      - Suggested Courses, circa 1944; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 9)
      - V-12, 1943; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 10)
    - Near East Conference, 1951-1953; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 11)
    - Newark College of Engineering, 1950-1952; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 12)
    - Newcomen Society, 1941-1952; 1953-1954; 2 folders (Box 12, Folder 13 to 14)
    - New Jersey, 1922-1951; 5 folders
      - Boiler Certificates, Etc, 1922-1924; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 15)
      - Defense Council, 1941; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 16)
      - Corporation Executives' Conference, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 17)
      - State Chamber of Commerce, 1950; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 18)
      - State Highway Department, 1944-1945; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 19)
    - New York University Inspection, 1949; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 20)
    - Nikolsky, Alexander A, 1942-1948; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 21)
    - North American Aviation Corporation, 1956-1957; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 22)
    - 'O' Miscellaneous, 1925-1953; 2 folders
      - 1925-1948, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 23)
      - 1943-1953, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 24)
    - Ohio Oil Company, 1940-1948; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 25)
    - Ohio Steel Foundry Company, 1951-1954; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 26)
    - Oljalvo, Morris Solomon, 1948-1958; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 27)
    - Olyphant, Murray Jr, 1947; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 28)
    - Open House Ad Hoc Committee, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 29)
    - Oriental Language Department, 1951; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 30)
    - Orientation Period, 1949-1952; 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 31)
    - 'P' Miscellaneous, 1941-1956; more than 10 folders
      - 1947-1950, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 32)
      - 1947-1949, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 33)
      - 1945-1947, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 34)
      - 1941-1945, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 35)
      - 1950, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 36)
      - 1951-1952, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 37)
      - 1952-1954, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 38)
      - 1953-1954, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 39)
      - 1954-1956, 2 folders (Box 12, Folder 40 to 41)
      - 1948-1955, 1 folder (Box 12, Folder 42)
    - Princeton and Educational Television, 1953; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Princeton University Fund, 1944; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Princeton University Third Century Fund (PUTCF), 1942-1953; 16 folders
      - III, 1948-1953; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 3)
      - II, 1946-1948; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 4)
      - I, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 5)
      - Committee for Corporation Lists, 1947; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 6)
      - Engineering Building Addition Contribution Letters, 1950; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 7)
      - Helm, Harold, 1949-1950; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 8)
      - Hildebrant, Walter G, 1942-1949; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 9)
      - Jameson, William A, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 10)
      - Jones J. P., Holding - Tucker, 1947; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 11)
      - McPherson, John G, 1947-1949; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 12)
      - Mestres, Ricardo A, 1948-1952; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 13)
      - Myers, Edward A, 1947-1949; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 14)
      - Opportunities - Special Gifts, 1945-1946; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 15)
      - Proctor, Carlton S, 1946-1950; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 16)
      - Whitney, Richard E, 1950-1952; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 17)
      - Miscellaneous, 1946-1950; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 18)
    - Controlled Materials and Products Priorities, 1951-1952; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 19)
    - Proctor and Gamble Company, 1948-1956; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 20)
    - Program for Servicemen, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 21)
    - Project Report for Dodds, 1946-1948; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 22)
    - Project Reports, 1949; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 23)
    - Project Research and Invention, Committee On, 1945-1954; more than 7 folders
      - Personnel Policies, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 24)
      - I, 1945-1953; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 25)
      - II, 1946-1950; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 26)
      - III, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 27)
      - IV, 1950-1954; 3 folders (Box 13, Folder 28 to 30)
      - Government Contracts (Woodrow), 1946-1951; 2 folders
        - 1949-1951, 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 31)
        - 1946-1948, 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 32)
    - Psychology Department, 1948; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 33)
    - Pure Oil Company, 1947-1951; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 34)
    - Purchasing Department, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 35)
    - Purchasing, 1945-1949; 1 folder (Box 13, Folder 36)
    - Parents' Day - Freshmen, 1949-1957; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Patent Policies, 1938-1945; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Patents, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Paul, George T, 1942-1948; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Paul, Joseph E, 1943; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Pease Company, C. F, 1938-1942; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Pennsylvania Railroad, 1944-1952; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Pennsylvania Turnpike, 1947-1948; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - Peyton, Bernard, 1952-1953; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Phi Beta Kappa, 1928-1929; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Phillips Exeter Academy, 1952; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Photographs, 1942; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Physical Education and Athletics, Department of, 1956; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - Pirnie, Malcolm, 1943-1946; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - Placement Bureau, 1951-1958; 2 folders
      - Teachers and Alumni, 1953-1958; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 15)
      - Sikes, Gordon G, 1951-1954; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Positions Available, 1944-1957; 7 folders
      - 1948, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 17)
      - 1947-1948, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 18)
      - 1944-1946, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 19)
      - Bachelor of Science in Engineering, Master of Science in Engineering, Doctor of Philosophy, 1951-1955; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 20)
      - Bachelor of Science in Engineering, Master of Science in Engineering, Doctor of Philosophy, 1952-1954; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 21)
      - Faculty, 1954-1957; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 22)
      - Industrial, 1955-1957; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 23)
    - Post-War International Problems - University Committee, 1943-1945; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 24)
    - Pratt, Wallace E, 1942-1944; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 25)
    - Pratt and Whitney, 1941-1943; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 26)
    - Preference Rating, 1942-1943; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 27)
    - Prentis, H. W. Jr, 1942; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 28)
    - President's Report, 1948-1954; 6 folders
      - 1948-1949, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 29)
      - 1949-1950, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 30)
      - 1950-1951, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 31)
      - 1951-1952, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 32)
      - 1952-1953, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 33)
      - 1953-1954, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Princeton Engineer, 1940-1952; 2 folders
      - 1940-1950, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 35)
      - Dean's Letter, 1943-1952; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Princeton University's Pension Scheme, 1945; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Procter Foundation, 1954-1957; 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Public Relations Department, 1931-1955; 2 folders
      - 1952-1955, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 39)
      - 1931-1952, 1 folder (Box 14, Folder 40)
    - 'R' Miscellaneous, 1944-1952; more than 3 folders
      - 1944-1948, 3 folders (Box 15, Folder 1 to 3)
      - 1949-1951, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 4)
      - 1951-1952, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Reaser, William E, 1952-1956; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Recorder, Office of the, 1952-1954; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Registrar, 1943-1953; 4 folders
      - Memos, Grades, Failure Statements, 1952-1953; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 8)
      - 1947-1951, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 9)
      - 1944-1950, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 10)
      - 1943-1948, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - Rensselaer Polytechnic Institute, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - Rentschler, Gordon S, 1941-1943; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 13)
    - Rentschler, Harvey C, 1947-1949; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 14)
    - Reports - Exam and Class, 1943-1945; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 15)
    - Research Activities, Engineering School, 1950; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 16)
    - Research Corporation, Annual Report, 1949-1950; 2 folders (Box 15, Folder 17 to 18)
    - Research Development Board (RDB), 1949-1953; 15 folders
      - Emergency Mobilization Unit, 1951 December 11-12; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 19)
      - Williams, E. Bryan, 1951-1953; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 20)
      - Service Equipment, Panel on, 1949-1953; 5 folders
        - Minutes, 1949; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 21)
        - Miscellaneous, 1952; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 22)
        - Camouflage - Ad Hoc Working Group, 1953; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 23)
        - Agenda, 1950-1953; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 24)
        - Maintenance Tools, Working Group on, 1953; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 25)
      - Memoranda to Executive Directors - Guidance Reports, 1949-1953; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 26)
      - French - Research Development Board, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 27)
      - Oxygen Work Group - Research Development Board, 1949-1952; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 28)
      - Space Heater Working Group, 1949-1953; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 29)
      - Firefighting Working Group - Research Development Board, 1949; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 30)
      - Prefabricated Structures, 1950-1953; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 31)
      - Equipment Materials Committee, 1949-1951; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 32)
      - Appointment and Security Data, 1949-1952; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 33)
    - Research Associates and Assistants - Lists, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 34)
    - Research Funds Faculty, 1944-1948; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 35)
    - Research Corporation, 1946-1949; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 36)
    - Reunion Forum, 1956; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 37)
    - Rheinstein, Alfred and Robert, 1941-1951; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 38)
    - Rhodes, John B, 1942-1945; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 39)
    - Ricketts, Louis D, 1922-1940; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 40)
    - Riker, Russell, 1948-1951; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 41)
    - Riparbelli, Carlo, 1946-1949; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 42)
    - Robins, Thomas, 1932-1950; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 43)
    - Rockefeller, Laurance S, 1941-1943; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 44)
    - Rowe, Robert Seaman, 1947-1956; 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 45)
    - Root, R. K, 1943-1946; 1942-1945; 2 folders (Box 15, Folder 46 to 47)
    - 'S' Miscellaneous, 1941-1954; portions of 2 boxes
      - 1941-1950, 4 folders (Box 15, Folder 48 to 51)
      - 1947-1948, 1 folder (Box 15, Folder 52)
      - 1947-1948, 2 folders (Box 16, Folder 1 to 2)
      - 1948-1949, 2 folders (Box 16, Folder 3 to 4)
      - 1950-1951, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 5)
      - 1950-1952, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 6)
      - 1952-1954, 2 folders (Box 16, Folder 7 to 8)
    - Sayre, Daniel C., 1941-1956; 3 folders
      - 1948-1956, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 9)
      - 1949-1950, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 10)
      - 1941-1949, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Engineering Scheduling, Fall, 1953; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Schedules and Schedule Committee, 1943-1945; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - Scholastic Guidance Committee, 1942-1943; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - Schureman, L. R, 1928-1941; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - Scribner, George K, 1945-1950; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - Selective Service System, 1941-1954; 2 folders
      - 1941-1943, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 17)
      - 1942-1954, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - Shepherd, George Woodthorpe, 1944-1951; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - T. Shriver and Company, Incorporated, 1947; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - Shop-Machine Engineering, 1943-1945; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - Shore, Sidney, 1947-1952; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - Sikes, Gordon G., 1941-1951; 3 folders
      - 1950-1951, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 23)
      - 1947-1950, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 24)
      - 1941-1947, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - Sikorsky, I. I, 1942-1943; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - Sillox, Louis Ketcham, 1935-1950; 5 folders
      - 1950, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 27)
      - 1947-1949, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 28)
      - 1945-1947, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 29)
      - 1942-1945, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 30)
      - 1935-1941, 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - Simmons, D. M, 1942-1950; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - Smith, H. Alexander, 1946-1948; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - Society for the Promotion of Engineering Education,1942-1946, dates not examined; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - Socony Vacuum Oil Company, 1940-1942; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - Soil Mechanics, 1937-1946; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - Soils Stabilization, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - Songs, Poems, Senior Faculty Dinners, 1948-1949; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - Soo, Shao-lee, 1953-1958; 1 folder (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - Spencer, Frank C, 1945-1949; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Sperry Gyroscope Company, 1942-1948; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Springfield Boiler Company, 1931-1940; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - Standard Oil Company, 1946-1950; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Steers, J. Rich, 1945-1950; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Stevens Institute of Technology, 1941-1954; 3 folders
      - 1950-1951, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 6)
      - 1941-1945, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 7)
      - 1951-1954, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - Stevenson Jordan and Harrison Incorporated, 1953-1954; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - Stine, C. M. A, 1935-1940; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - Straus, Roger W, 1942-1949; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Studebaker, J. W, 1940; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - Student Employment - Warfield, Richard, 1937-1942; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - Summer Job Program, 1947; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Summer Positions for Faculty, 1957; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Summer Reading Lists and Reports, 1938-1942; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Supple, Henderson L, 1950-1951; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 17)
    - Survey of Education at Princeton, 1946-1947; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 18)
    - 'T' Miscellaneous, 1942-1954; 7 folders
      - 1949-1950, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 19)
      - 1948-1949, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 20)
      - 1950-1951, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 21)
      - 1946-1948, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 22)
      - 1942-1946, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 23)
      - 1951-1952, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 24)
      - 1952-1954, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Tan, E. K, 1943-1944; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Taplin, Frank E, 1957-1959; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 27)
    - Taylor, Hugh S, 1935-1950; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 28)
    - Teaching Techniques, Faculty Meeting Notes, P. E. Dicker Report, 1948; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Tests, Standard Prices for, 1922-1942; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Texas Company, 1951-1953; 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 31)
    - Textile Research Institute, 1944-1955; 2 folders
      - 1953-1955, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 32)
      - 1944-1953, 1 folder (Box 17, Folder 33)